Guide to the Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
Stevens family papers, [ca. 1775-2010]
- Series III. Frederick Charles Stevens Generation
  - III-A. Frederick Charles Stevens (formerly Charles Frederick) (1856-1916)
    - Business Correspondence
      - Correspondence: Copybook "14," with index, Feb.2, 1909-Apr.7, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "15," with index, Apr.7, 1909-May 21, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "16," with index, May 24, 1909-Aug.23, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "17," with index, Aug.24, 1909-Nov.12, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "18," with index, Nov.12, 1909-Jan.20, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "19," with index, Jan.20, 1910-Apr.25, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "20," with index, Apr.26, 1910-June 19, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "21," with index, June 20, 1910-Sep.24, 1910 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "22," with index, Sep.24, 1910-Dec.12, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence: Copybook "23," with index, Dec.12, 1910-Jan. 1911 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business, Dec.6, 1909-Oct.31, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business, Nov.1-21, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business, Nov.22, 1910-Dec. 1910 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business, Jan. 1911 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business, Feb-June 1911 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business, July 1911-Nov.12, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence: Telephone business (and small amount of tax correspondence), Nov.21, 1911-1918 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence: Mostly Garrison Babcock, V.P., North Electric Co., 1909-March 1912 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence: Stocks, Patents, Competitors, 1913-January 1915 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Financial Documents/Business Documents
      - Gurley & Stevens: Daybook, 1890-1891 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Gurley & Stevens: Daybook, 1891-1892 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Gurley & Stevens: Account book, 1890-1891 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Gurley & Stevens: Account book, 1891-1892 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Daybook, 1892-1894 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Daybook, 1894-1897 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Daybook, 1898-1901 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Daybook, 1901-1904 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Account book, 1892-1894 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Account book, 1894-1897 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Account book, 1898-1904 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - F.C. Stevens, Washington office: Account book (1898-1904) - loose papers, 1899-1903 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Stevens & Stevens: Bills receivable book, 1894-1898 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Stevens & Stevens: Bills receivable book (1894- 1898) - Loose papers, 1899-1903 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Baldwin Electric Meter Co.: Daybook, 1894-1897 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Baldwin Electric Meter Co.: Account book, 1894-1897 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Baldwin Electric Meter Co.: Statement of shop expenses, 1896-1897 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Baldwin Electric Meter Co.: Check book, 1895-1897 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Citizens National Bank: Statements & Stockholders lists, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Cassava Products Co.: Patents/Contracts, 1910-1911 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Cassava Products Co.: Patents/Contracts, 1912-1915 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Telephone business: Patents/Contracts, 1910-1916 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Woodward & Lothrop: Insurance policies, 1892-1894 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Account book - Personal, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Checks/Bank statements: Federal National Bank; First National Bank, 1913-1914 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Receipts/Bills: Stable construction, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Receipts/Bills: House construction, 1890-1892 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Receipts/Bills: "F.C. Stevens, Treas.", 1890-1892 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Receipts/Bills, 1891-1893 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Receipts/Bills, 1902-June 1903 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Receipts/Bills, July 1903-1904 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Proposal for Automanual System in Kansas, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Documents related to the Commonwealth of Australia's Postmaster General's Department Schedule No. 154, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Documents assigning rights of 2 telephone companies to F. C. Stevens, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Statements of Income and Expenses, Factory Expenses and Overhead, and Balance Sheet, 1911- August 31, 1913 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous Business Documents, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Personal Papers
      - Correspondence, 1867-1875, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Estate papers, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Estate papers: Report and proceedings of appraiser, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Estate papers: Receipts, 1914-1917 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Certificates and programs, n.d., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Wedding invitation, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1879-1917, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Telephony (Journal), 1914, 1914, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Autograph book, 1861-1921 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Belle C. Stevens: Social notebook, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous: Phrenology reading (copy), 1875 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous: Property sketch, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - III-B. Doris Reynolds May (1887-1974)
    - Correspondence, 1895-1903 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Sept. 1904-Oct.8, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Oct.13-20, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Oct.22-31, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Nov.4-11, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Nov.16-30, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Dec.2-15, 1904 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Jan.6-21, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Jan.22-30, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Feb.2-12, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, Feb.17-28, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Mar.2-15, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Mar.17-29, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Apr.1-29, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, May 4-16, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, May 20-29, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, June 8-30, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1906-1914 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, Feb.1915-Nov.15, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, Nov.16-21, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Dec.2-31, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Series IV. Robert Sproule Stevens Generation
  - IV-A. Robert Sproule Stevens (1888-1968)
    - Cornell Law School Papers
      - A, B, C - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - G, H, I - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - J, K, L, M - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - N, O, P, Q - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - R, S, T, U - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - V, W, X, Y, Z - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Myron Taylor smoking; Committee on graduate and special students (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Myron Taylor Hall facilities (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Myron Taylor Tower & Keys (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - University Curriculum (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Curriculum Committee (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Curriculum Committee - First year curriculum (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Curriculum Committee, etc. (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Curriculum (1) (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Curriculum (1): Class on Unfair Competition (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Curriculum (2) (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Interdepartmental curriculum arrangements (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Law School outlines of courses (1) (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Law School outlines of courses (2) (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Law School outlines of courses (3) (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Professor Henns' course outlines (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Cooperative law (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - International law and diplomacy (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - Patent law (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - Patent law: Notes from class on Patent Law for engineers (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Legal Aid: including George Junior Republic- Pyle (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Government investigations (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - War contract termination (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - War contract termination (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - JAG-OCS - War contract (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - General problem courses (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - University Subcommittee of Policy Committee on Special Curricula for Veterans; Ohio Survey of Veterans' Wishes (Box 20, Folder 29)
      - Revision of entrance requirements: veterans credit for training and experience in service (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Military data - Law School alumni & former students (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - President (Box 20, Folder 32)
      - Emeritus professors (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - Provost Committee (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - Fundraising Committee (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - Committee on Budget (Box 20, Folder 36)
      - Faculty Representatives' vote (Box 20, Folder 37)
      - University rulings affecting faculty tenure, promotions, war leaves, retirement (Box 20, Folder 38)
      - Report to Alumni (Box 20, Folder 39)
      - Promotion and publicity (Box 20, Folder 40)
      - CLS - Pre-1956 - Dormitory (Box 20, Folder 41)
      - Tuition 1946 (Box 20, Folder 42)
      - Enrollments eastern law schools (Box 20, Folder 43)
      - Industrial and labor relations - Corning Program (Box 20, Folder 44)
      - Graduate Record Exams (Box 20, Folder 45)
      - Law School papers (Box 20, Folder 46)
      - Law School papers (Box 20, Folder 47)
      - Cornell Law School miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 48)
      - Miscellaneous reports (Box 20, Folder 49)
      - Papers of Professor Thompson (Box 20, Folder 50)
      - Law Association Committee on Communication with law school, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 51)
      - Papers concerning Professor Willard B. Cowles (Box 20, Folder 52)
      - Recruitment: Correspondence with deans, lists, reports, etc. (Box 20, Folder 53)
      - Recruitment (Box 20, Folder 54)
      - Names of possible persons (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Federal Employment Papers
      - Federal employment, 1942-1945 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, September-November 1942 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, December-1942 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, January-March 1943 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, April-June 1943 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, July-August 1943 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, September 1943 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, October 1943 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, November-December 15, 1943 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, December 16, 1943-January 1944 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, February 1944 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, March-April 1944 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, May-June 1944 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, July-August 1944 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, September-October 1944 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, November-December 1944 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, January-February 1945 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - The Telechronometer Company, The Telephone Improvement Company, and the North Electric Company
      - Correspondence, June-December 1916 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, January 1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, February 1917 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, March-1917 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, April-1917 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, May-June 1917 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Personal Papers
      - Diary, 1910-1912 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Diary, 1914-1915 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Notebook with jokes and thoughts (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1899 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, January-1917 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, February-1917 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, March-1917 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, April-1917 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1917, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1920s (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence regarding the publication of Pauline Croll Stevens' poems upon her death, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1941-1949 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Autograph book, 1882-1907 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Autograph book loose letters, 1903-1927 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Autograph book loose letters, 1930-1937 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Autograph book loose letters, 1938-1966 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Autograph book, 1961-1968 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Certificate of Attorney and Counsellor-at-Law, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Certificate of honorable discharge from the U.S. Army, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Certificate of matrimony between Robert Sproule Stevens and Helen Pauline Croll, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Certificate of merit in World War II, 1947 (Box ??, Folder Cons)
      - Certificate of life membership in the American Law Institute, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Norwood Institute Honor Roll for March, with Helen Stevens' name on it (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Lend-Lease Administration; recognition, 1941-1943 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Retirement from Cornell Law deanship, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Gift book of letters presented upon his retirement as Dean, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Gifts to Cornell Law School, 1963-1964 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Financial records and receipts, 1907-1908 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Financial records and receipts, 1920s-1930s (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Financial correspondence, misc., 1914-1948 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - New York State Income Tax forms and notes, 1924-1925 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1951-1968 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Appearances in Cornell publications, 1958-1988 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - The Cornell Law Forum, with article "Dean Stevens Retires: At Cornell 1919-1954" (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Author's proof from article "Stevens of Cornell: A Man For All Seasons" from the American Bar, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Funeral and Estate Papers
      - Travel abroad, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Funeral paperwork, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Memorial speeches, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - Memorial papers, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Will, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - Sympathy cards and notes, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Obituaries and biography, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - Memorial Fund, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - Estate paperwork - correspondence with E. W. Dann Stevens, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Estate paperwork, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Estate paperwork, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Estate paperwork - final accounting, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Estate paperwork, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - IV-B. (Helen) Pauline Croll Stevens (1885-1936)
    - Personal Papers and Writings
      - Diaries (2), 1903, 1903-1904 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Diaries (2), 1904, 1905-1906 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Diary, 1906-1907 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Diary, 1924-1935 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Poetry journal, 1899-1900 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Poetry journals (2), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Poetry: Just For You - manuscript, n.d. (Box 40, Folder -)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Poetry: "Where Sunbeams Dwell", n.d. (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Poetry, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Poetry: Transcript of memorial radio broadcast, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Poetry of Antonia Schwab Mills, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - "An account of the trip around the world" (of RSpS, RCS, and PCS) - typescript, 1935-36 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - "An account of the trip around the world" (of RSpS, RCS, and PCS) - transcript, 1935-36 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Writing: "Out in the West", ca.1895 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - School notebook, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - School notebook: "Rhetoric II", 1900 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Drawings, 1908, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Scrapbook, 1922-1933 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Certificates, 1903, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Estate Papers
      - Will and deeds of trust, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Will and deeds of trust, 1934-1941 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Envelope marked "Re Estate of Pauline C. Stevens, estate tax, etc.", 1936 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - "Re estate of Pauline C. Stevens", 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - "Re estate of Pauline C. Stevens", 1934-1939 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Bank book, 1936-1941 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Final accounting, 1936-1941 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Final accounting, 1936-1939 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Final accounting, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Final accounting, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Final accounting - Correspondence regarding distribution of trust, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Guardian accounting, 1940-1945 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Guardian accounting, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Original trust account (vouchers for purchases by trust account), 1939-1956 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1937-1941 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1938-1940 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Vouchers, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1951-1952 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Trustee's accounting, 1953-1954 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Trustee's list of securities, 1939-1951 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Trustee accounts regarding securities, 1936-1941 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Trustee accounts bills, papers, correspondence, 1936-1944 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Federal and NY estate tax 1937, 1934-1944 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Federal and NY estate tax 1937, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Guardian taxes, 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Trustee taxes, 1942-1943 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Trustee taxes, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Trustee taxes, 1946-1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Trustee taxes, 1949-1951 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Trustee taxes, 1952-1954 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1936-May 1937 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, June 1937-Sept 1938 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Oct 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Manchester property (also deals with the estate of Albert Ivins Croll), 1934 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Manchester property, 1935 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Manchester property, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Manchester property, 1940-1943 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Manchester property, Jan-July 1944 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Manchester property, Aug 1944-1947 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Manchester property - Insurance policies, 1936-1943 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - IV-C. Eva (Loomis) Howe Stevens (1892-1988)
    - Personal Papers
      - Diary "A Line a Day, Five Year Diary", 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Diary "A line a Day": Loose papers, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Travel diary, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Travel diary: Loose papers, n.d. (1955) (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Marriage certificate, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - Guest book: Nantucket, MA, 1951-1980 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Newspaper clippings and obituary, 1937-1943, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous: Christmas card, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Charitable Donations
      - Gifts and contributions, 1965-1981 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Gifts and contributions, 1982-1987 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Community Partners for Youth, Inc., 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Cornell Plantations: Correspondence, 1981-1995 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Cornell Plantations: Brochures, newsletters, articles, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Cornell Plantations: Brochure, Xeroxes, 1983, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Newspaper clippings: Flood of 1981 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Cornell University: 208 Hanshaw Road, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Cornell University: Builders of Cornell, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - Cornell University: Eva Howe Stevens Scholarship Fund, 1970-1992 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Cornell University: Grandfather clock and Painting, 1970-1986 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Cornell University: Robert S. Stevens Fund, 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Rochester Museum & Science Center, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Estate Papers
      - John B. Howe committee: Correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - John B. Howe committee: Court petitions, 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - John B. Howe committee: Lincoln Rochester Trust Company account, 1955-1959 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - John B. Howe estate, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - John B. Howe estate, Jan-May 1961 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - John B. Howe estate, June 1961-Feb 1962 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - John B. Howe estate, Mar-Aug 1962 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - John B. Howe estate, Sep 1962-1963, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - IV-D. Helen Lee Stevens Gregory (1880-1953)
    - Diary, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, with authors' autographs, 1882-1914, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - IV-E. Marian Stevens (1885-1975)
    - Papers
      - Correspondence, 1940-1949 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Travel remembrances, To Marian from K.W.D., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Estate papers, 1965-1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Estate papers: Donation to The National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - "Line A Day" diary of Marian Stevens, January 1, 1904 - December 31, 1908, with a bound edited transcript by Jane K. and Robert C. Stevens and Ann H. (also a CD containing a copy of transcript) Stevens, 1904-1908 (Box 92)
    - Artwork
      - Painting of Pauline C. Stevens, n.d. (Box ??, Folder Cons)
      - Drawings/Sketches, ca.1915, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Sketches: Dresses (with fabric samples), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Sketch book: Telling the story of the "T.R.'s" (Truly Rurals) who went West to meet the "G.T.'s" (Globe Trotters (the two F.C.S's)) on their return from around the world, 1912 (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Sketch book: Costume events at Maplewood, 1914-1916 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Sketch book: "The Freddyssy", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Sketch book: "Two Little Chaps to Europe...", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Sketch book, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 41)